

# Ueslei Santos Lima

Software Developer

uesleisantoslima@gmail.com				
+55 79 996442111				

www.linkedin.com/in/uesleilima



www.uesleilima.com



Analyst and developer of information technology systems, with leadership skills and experience in web, mobile, embedded and service oriented systems, as also in financial transaction authorization systems. Fast learner and easily adaptable. Enthusiast of agile software development process.

# Work Experience

# 02/2015 - Present **System Analyst**

### Banese Bank

Bank of Sergipe State

#### Tasks/Achievements

- System analyst and backend developer (JEE), development of the core financial transaction authorization system
- Integration testing automatization (IBM Rational Integration Tester expert)
- Team alternate Scrum Master (2x)
- Helped to bring automatized tests and process-structured code-review to the team;

03/2014 - 02/2015

Sao Paulo, Brazil

Aracaju, Brazil

### Software Engineer

#### **HP Inc**

Hewlett-Packard's Brazil R&D Branch

#### Tasks/Achievements

- Software Engineer of FutureSmart Multi-function Printer Firmware
- Frontend/backend development of the Web application interface. (C# / JavaScript)
- Web services maintenance and development
- Active participant of R&D discussion groups and development of ideas

06/2014 - Present

Sorocaba, Brazil

## Software Developer

#### Mikromatica Group

#### Tasks/Achievements

- Development of ASP.NET / WebForms / C# / Entity
   Framework application for Metrology management and database maintenance
- Microsoft Azure hosting and monitoring

02/2013 - 02/2014

Sorocaba, Brazil

## **System Engineer**

## CESAR - Recife Advanced Systems and Research Center

#### Tasks/Achievements

- Software and systems engineering, Java (JSE/Swing) development, distributed systems architecture design;
- Windows Mobile application entire life-cycle development (Conception, brainstorming, benchmarking and coding in XAML/C#)

02/2012 - 02/2013

Itabuna, Brazil

## **Software Development Analyst**

### Intellisys Informática Ltda

#### Tasks/Achievements

- CRM system Web application frontend/backend development and database maintenance
- Mobile application conception, analysis and development (Android)

# **Skills & Competences**

Java Programming	T.	1	1
.NET / C# Development			
, ,			
Web APIs Development			
Scrum / Agile			
Software Engineering			
Leadership			

## **Education**

Bachelor in Computer Science (03/2007 - 06/2012) University of Santa Cruz - UESC

## Certificates

Secure Software Development (11/2016 - 11/2016)

Microsoft Certified Solutions Developer - Programming in HTML5 with JavaScript and CSS3 (01/2013 - Present)

Agile for IT Professionals (08/2012 - 08/2012)

Scrum and XP: Best practices for project management success. (03/2011 - 03/2011)

WEB Development with ASP.NET e C# (05/2010 - 05/2010)

# **Organizations**

Computer Science Academic Center (04/2011 - 04/2012)
President

# Languages

English Expert

Portuguese Native or Bilingual

## **Interests**

IoT | AI | Cloud Computing | Software Architecture | BPM | SOA | Omni-Channel